‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎CHEONSAN UNIT, GANGWON PROVINCE
‎Two of our covert operatives
‎and a diplomat
‎were killed in succession
‎in Singapore, Hong Kong, and Japan.
‎All were operatives secretly setting up
‎the inter-Korean peace talks.
‎The one behind the assassinations
‎was hard-liner
‎Deputy Director Kim Jeong Seon
‎of the General Bureau of Intelligence
‎on South Korea.
‎Eliminate him.
‎Show him the brutal price
‎of crossing us.
‎Get out.
‎In the passenger seat.
‎This is where you and I will both die.
‎-What the hell?
‎-Hey!
‎Korea People's TV reported this morning
‎that an impulsive act
‎by a North Korean People's Army officer
‎killed hard-liner
‎Deputy Director Kim Jeong Seon
‎of the General Bureau of Intelligence
‎on South Korea.
‎A so-called military officer
‎conspired with hostile forces to target
‎our nation's veteran revolutionary,
‎Deputy Director Comrade Kim Jeong Seon…
‎The identity of the North Korean officer
‎remains unknown,
‎and they are reported
‎to have died together.
‎-Last year, Deputy Director Kim…
‎-Well, well.
‎I guess he really wanted to
‎get discharged.
‎…he was also the driving force
‎behind the systemization.
‎OB-GYN SURGERY CENTER
‎EPISODE 2
‎Excuse me, I'm Im Yu-jin's husband.
‎Just a moment, please.
‎She's in labor right now.
‎It's that way.
‎OB-GYN OPERATING ROOM
‎You have to keep breathing.
‎-You're doing well. Breathe!
‎-Good.
‎I know you're tired, but keep breathing.
‎You're almost there.
‎I'm here for Im Yu-jin.
‎She's in surgery right now.
‎-Doctor.
‎-The baby is healthy.
‎But the mother…
‎Yu-jin.
‎Let's name our child…
‎Min-ji.
‎Forget everything,
‎leave the past behind…
‎and live as Min-ji's dad.
‎Raise our Min-ji…
‎to be someone who can be loved…
‎and someone who can give love.
‎Like any father in this world…
‎who would do anything
‎for his daughter…
‎I want you
‎to live
‎as the father of our daughter…
‎Min-ji.
‎Let me go!
‎Sergeant Kim.
‎Put down the gun.
‎You're only making things worse!
‎Let me go.
‎Discharge me right now!
‎We'll pretend this never happened.
‎So calm down, okay?
‎You promised me my freedom
‎if I completed this mission.
‎You said that the last two times.
‎I've done everything
‎you people told me to do up until now…
‎just to survive.
‎If you go back on your word again…
‎I'm prepared to wipe out this unit
‎and take you all down with me.
‎Okay, okay.
‎I'll grant your discharge.
‎That's not a problem.
‎So just calm down, okay?
‎Calm down.
‎FORMULA FEEDING METHOD AND CARE
‎There, there.
‎Let me rest a bit.
‎Leave the past behind…
‎Hold on.
‎Hey, Han-soo.
‎Min-ji has a fever.
‎Let's see here.
‎Gosh, that stinks.
‎Daddy.
‎And live as Min-ji's dad.
‎Daddy!
‎Daddy?
‎Raise our Min-ji
‎to be someone who can be loved…
‎He straightens his crooked tie
‎And even through the endless, tiring days
‎He finds his strength and walks on
‎Nothing can stop him
‎My dad is the best
‎-…and someone who can give love.
‎-Daddy!
‎Daddy!
‎Min-ji!
‎Like any father in this world…
‎who would do anything
‎-for his daughter…
‎-One, two, three!
‎-Thank you!
‎Take a photo with me, Dad.
‎Come on, hurry!
‎Sorry!
‎I want you
‎to live…
‎MYEONGEUN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
‎28TH GRADUATION CEREMONY
‎Dad!
‎…as the father of our daughter,
‎Min-ji.
‎Dad…
‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎LAST NIGHT
‎That's him.
‎Hey, are you Kim Nam-hoon?
‎Who are you?
‎That's none of your business. Come here.
‎Let's go over there and have a chat.
‎Go easy on him, man.
‎Min-ji, Min-ji.
‎"I have something to tell you."
‎"I'll be at the back gate at school."
‎"I'll wait until you get here."
‎I have something to tell you.
‎I'll be at the back gate at school.
‎I'll wait until you get here.
‎NO UNAUTHORIZED ENTRY
‎-Kim Min-ji!
‎-Hey!
‎Min-ji!
‎You really came.
‎-She actually came.
‎-I can't believe you showed up.
‎-Min-ji, Min-ji!
‎-Hey, Min-ji.
‎She actually showed up.
‎I have bad news.
‎Nam-hoon isn't feeling well,
‎so he can't come.
‎-Oh no.
‎-You okay?
‎Don't worry. We're here for you, Min-ji.
‎That was a good slap.
‎Nice!
‎What the hell are you staring at,
‎you filthy trash?
‎I thought this was over.
‎Get me transferred or expelled.
‎Do whatever you want.
‎Just ask your dad to do it.
‎I don't want to.
‎I'm going to make you get on your knees.
‎Sorry,
‎but I'm different from my dad.
‎Oh.
‎Are you?
‎Try hitting me again.
‎That's hilarious.
‎Go ahead.
‎Hit me, Min-ji. I said hit me!
‎Let go of me!
‎-Come on! Hit her! Hit her!
‎-Hit her!
‎-Hey!
‎-Come on!
‎You crazy bitch!
‎Yeah, so what?
‎Let go!
‎Hye-ri, are you okay?
‎You thought I wouldn't hit you
‎because you're a girl?
‎They say birds of a feather
‎flock together.
‎You're all so trashy.
‎Look at you, ganging up to beat up a girl.
‎-You got this. Come on!
‎-Hey!
‎-You have a death wish?
‎-Let go!
‎Damn it, just die!
‎Min-ji!
‎-Get up, Min-ji!
‎-Stop messing around.
‎You little!
‎-Hey, Min-ji!
‎-That's no fun.
‎-There's blood.
‎-Blood?
‎-Oh, crap. Wait.
‎-Oh, shit.
‎-Goddamn it.
‎-Hold on.
‎-Is she really dead?
‎-Damn it.
‎-It's blood.
‎-Damn it!
‎What's going on?
‎You're kidding, right?
‎Hey.
‎Hey!
‎Dad…
‎-Is she really dead?
‎-Damn it.
‎Goddamn it.
‎DAD
‎Someone call an ambulance.
‎I'll do it.
‎Stop right there. Don't do anything!
‎-You're all accomplices.
‎-What are you talking about?
‎Screw you. You all came here to trash her.
‎If I get caught,
‎I'll report every single one of you.
‎Dad…
‎I have nothing to lose.
‎So think carefully.
‎Collect everyone's phones already.
‎-What for?
‎-Why are you taking our phones?
‎Hey, don't worry.
‎It'll be okay. I know who to call.
‎They might be able to help, okay?
‎-Look who it is.
‎-Hello, sir.
‎Hey, punk!
‎Collect all the money
‎by the end of the month.
‎Charge a bit more interest
‎and keep the difference.
‎Yes, sir. And here.
‎I brought you this week's collection.
‎Well, look at you.
‎-Good job.
‎-Excuse me.
‎What is it?
‎SOUTH SIDE COLLECTOR
‎GOLDEN TEETH GANG, OH MIN-CHEOL
‎Hello, sir.
‎I accidentally…
‎I mean, we accidentally killed someone.
‎So what?
‎Is there any way to take care of the body?
‎Are you insane?
‎How the hell can I do that?
‎Then could we ask someone higher up?
‎My dad is Ju Gang-chan,
‎the chairman of Juhak Construction.
‎I'll pay whatever you want,
‎so just get rid of the body.
‎Hey.
‎You expect me to believe your dad
‎is the chairman of Juhak Construction?
‎Get lost!
‎Hey, kid.
‎Hello, boss.
‎Who were you talking to?
‎Oh, just one of my boys.
‎-His name is Min-ho--
‎-No, no.
‎You just said something
‎about Juhak Construction.
‎Oh, some crazy kid was bullshitting
‎that her dad is the chairman
‎of Juhak Construction.
‎What exactly did she do?
‎She accidentally killed someone
‎and asked me to get rid of the body.
‎I think some punks just screwed up.
‎Don't worry about it, sir.
‎Call her back
‎and tell her I'll help.
‎Excuse me?
‎I said call her back.
‎Yes, sir.
‎Oh jeez. Right here, boss.
‎My goodness.
‎Man, this poor little thing…
‎Move out of the way.
‎Goodness.
‎Why do you look so scared, Ms. Princess?
‎You're nothing like your father.
‎Money isn't a problem.
‎I'll give you as much as you want.
‎Come on now.
‎I have a lot of money.
‎I usually don't bother
‎with things like this.
‎But I owe Chairman Ju,
‎so I'm making an exception to help you.
‎I don't care!
‎Just make sure no one finds out.
‎Tell me.
‎You can take care of the body, right?
‎Hey!
‎You know what? You talk just like him.
‎You're definitely Chairman Ju's daughter.
‎Hey.
‎Don't worry.
‎We just need to slice her open,
‎pull out her guts,
‎stitch her back up nicely,
‎and throw her into the sea.
‎That's it.
‎Nobody will find her.
‎Boss, why bother pulling out the guts?
‎It gets so messy.
‎Come on, you sound like an amateur.
‎You have to remove the organs
‎so the body doesn't float to the surface.
‎And if it's buried in the mountains,
‎wild animals won't dig it up, you idiot.
‎Got it, boss.
‎You see, wild animals sniff out
‎and eat the organs first.
‎-Hey, Gang-min.
‎-Yes?
‎Let's have soju
‎and blood sausage after this.
‎-I'm craving organ meats.
‎-Sounds great, sir.
‎Boss, I want extra liver.
‎I want extra rice.
‎What about you, kid?
‎I've already eaten, sir.
‎You have?
‎All right, you're home.
‎Look at that. What a nice house.
‎Excuse me, Ms. Get-Rid-of-The-Body.
‎Let's keep this a secret from your father.
‎It won't be good for either of us
‎if we worry him for no good reason.
‎Keep your promise.
‎Gang-min, let's go pull out some guts.
‎Yes, boss.
‎Bye, pretty girl.
‎Tell me.
‎Where's Min-ji?
‎Where is she?
‎Oh Min-cheol…
‎I was just trying to scare her,
‎but she fell while running away.
‎I'm sorry.
‎Keep talking.
‎I called Min-cheol.
‎I don't know what happened after that
‎because I ran away too.
‎Please, you have to believe me.
‎Oh Min-cheol.
‎Where is he right now?
‎Dad.
‎What's going on?
‎You didn't go to work?
‎Why did you get soaked in the rain?
‎What's the matter with you?
‎I'm hungry. Is there anything to eat?
‎SANGSAENG SAVINGS BANK
‎Well, this is new.
‎He's never been late before.
‎Have you heard from Kim?
‎BREAK ROOM
‎I'll try calling him.
‎SANG-A
‎I'm sorry.
‎Please give me another chance.
‎Please let my daughter go.
‎Please.
‎You think this is a joke, mister?
‎If you borrow money,
‎you have to pay it back.
‎Hey, Hong-sik.
‎I think we need to refresh his memory.
‎Read him the contract.
‎"If I fail to pay back the money
‎within the agreed period,
‎I will sign over
‎my family members' organs."
‎-Dad!
‎-No!
‎No, no, no! That's not true!
‎There was nothing like that
‎in the contract!
‎It's called a special clause.
‎Dad!
‎I added the special clause.
‎Please forgive me! Spare my daughter!
‎Please!
‎Goddamn it, you're getting blood on me!
‎-Damn it.
‎-Not my daughter…
‎Hey, mister.
‎I'm pretty sure
‎students have organs too.
‎Hey, kid. Come here.
‎Come on.
‎-No, no, no.
‎-Hey.
‎Look up.
‎Eyes, heart, kidneys, and pancreas.
‎Looks like she has them all. Take her.
‎-Dad! Dad!
‎-No! No, please!
‎Dad!
‎-Get in there.
‎-Dad!
‎Get away from me!
‎-Go away!
‎-It'll be over quickly.
‎Go away!
‎It'll only take a second.
‎No, stop! Stop it!
‎-Did you order delivery?
‎-Sorry?
‎Did you order delivery?
‎Hong-sik ordered macarons earlier
‎but canceled them.
‎Macarons? Seriously, Hong-sik?
‎But I canceled the order.
‎Maybe they got the wrong house.
‎Hey, send them away.
‎Okay.
‎Close the door behind you just in case.
‎Hey, go check it out.
‎On it.
‎Is she under yet?
‎What was that?
‎What's that noise?
‎Hey, Hong-sik.
‎Please spare me. I'm not with them.
‎Please don't kill me.
‎What the hell? Is he a cop?
‎Who the hell set that up?
‎What the hell? Damn it!
‎Who the hell are you, bastard?
‎SAFE AND HAPPY DOWON POLICE STATION
‎Excuse me.
‎Excuse me!
‎Why am I here?
‎I didn't fight anyone.
‎Excuse me.
‎Hey, mister!
‎Be quiet, will you?
‎You have to wait until we finish
‎examining the CCTV footage.
‎Is that really necessary?
‎Let me reiterate
‎that I didn't lay a finger on any of them.
‎All I did was stop that wild boar
‎from going on a rampage.
‎Excuse me!
‎Hey, mister!
‎I…
‎Hey, you punk!
‎Explain to him what happened!
‎Tell him you lost your mind
‎and acted alone!
‎Mister, is that bastard
‎sleeping right now?
‎In this situation?
‎Are you serious?!
‎EVERYONE, I SAW IT!
‎I SAW A FULL-ON STREET BRAWL!
‎NEVER SEEN A 17-TO-1 FIGHT BEFORE
‎Oh my goodness.
‎Here you go.
‎What's so interesting?
‎This man is amazing. Here, watch.
‎Goodness, he's just barbaric.
‎Right, he is.
‎My word.
‎Oh dear.
‎GENERAL BUREAU OF INTELLIGENCE
‎ON SOUTH KOREA
‎MEDIA SURVEILLANCE ROOM
‎MANGYUN-DONG BBQ RESTAURANT ASSAULT
‎TATTOOED THUGS GETTING CRUSHED
‎BY MIDDLE-AGED MARINE GUY
‎THREAT LEVEL
‎TIER ONE
‎A tier-one wanted fugitive
‎has been caught on camera.
‎WHO IS THE CITIZEN WHO SHUT DOWN
‎THE TROUBLEMAKERS AT A BBQ RESTAURANT?
‎MOST WANTED FUGITIVE
‎THREAT LEVEL: TIER ONE
‎That spy son of a bitch.
‎I thought he was dead,
‎but he turned up like a ghost.
‎We should head to the South
‎and bring back his head immediately.
‎-Arm the infiltration team.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎Hold on.
‎We can't do that.
‎The high-level inter-Korean talks
‎are less than a month away.
‎Carrying out a covert operation
‎at a time like this
‎won't do us any good.
‎I agree.
‎It would be best to officially request
‎cooperation from the South.
‎We'll have our operatives
‎accompany the delegation
‎and make the arrest then.
‎I agree.
‎Have you all lost your minds?
‎Have you forgotten
‎what that bastard did to the Republic?
‎GENERAL BUREAU OF INTELLIGENCE
‎ON SOUTH KOREA
‎DIRECTOR GENERAL RI EUNG RYEONG
‎Comrade Director General,
‎you're out of line!
‎Do you want your head to roll first?
‎That bastard is a traitor to the regime
‎who's become a lapdog for the South!
‎Shut it!
‎That's enough.
‎Follow the orders of the Party.
‎DIRECTOR GENERAL RI EUNG RYEONG
‎They may be highly decorated,
‎but they're still wet behind the ears.
‎They've grown soft from peacetime
‎and lost their minds.
‎Since when have we had to tiptoe around
‎the bastards in the South?
‎Those damn greenhorns
‎think they can arrest him?
‎It's impossible to capture that man alive.
‎Don't you think our warriors
‎are more than up for the task?
‎Not a chance.
‎Unless it's someone like Park Yeong Gwang.
‎Park Yeong Gwang?
‎Are you referring to Number 66?
‎That's right, 66.
‎He truly deserved the title
‎of the greatest warrior
‎in our unit's history.
‎He single-handedly took out
‎an entire South Korean commando platoon.
‎But didn't Park Yeong Gwang
‎die in action a long time ago?
‎Damn it.
‎If only that traitor
‎hadn't stabbed him in the back…
‎Hey.
‎Isn't Park Yeong Gwang's younger brother
‎one of our operatives?
‎Yes, sir. He's an elite warrior
‎who's just as skilled as Number 66.
‎Is that so?
‎How fortunate.
‎Bring him to me now.
‎Yes, sir.
‎His older brother had his number stolen,
‎so it's up to him to get it back.
‎Naturally.
‎REPUBLIC OF KOREA
‎SPECIAL MISSIONS DIRECTORATE
‎Director, we have a situation.
‎Report.
‎Unusual activity involving Agent Kim,
‎our top surveillance subject,
‎has been reported.
‎Unusual activity?
‎Name, Park Jin-cheol. Former ROK soldier.
‎On active duty, he infiltrated the North
‎on multiple missions with Agent Kim.
‎His military record includes
‎three airstrike operations
‎against Palestine,
‎the elimination
‎of the radical militant group, LSS,
‎serving in Operation Indira
‎to decimate a Pakistani terrorist group,
‎-defensive combat operations in--
‎-Hey.
‎You think I don't know
‎who Park Jin-cheol is?
‎Just report the situation.
‎Footage of Park Jin-cheol's rampage
‎three days ago
‎was captured by North Korean intelligence,
‎exposing Agent Kim who was with him.
‎You've got to be kidding me.
‎CODENAME MOLE CRICKET
‎SMD DIRECTOR KANG GUK-CHEOL
‎RESTRICTED AREA
‎The North issued an official arrest notice
‎through the hotline 45 minutes ago.
‎They've requested North Korean operatives
‎to enter the country
‎during the high-level inter-Korean talks.
‎Sir, this is unacceptable.
‎This means giving spies free rein
‎to roam our country.
‎The government denies
‎Agent Kim's existence,
‎but the longer we stall, the more likely
‎they'll have to grant the North's request.
‎We can't hand over someone
‎as dangerous as Kim to the North.
‎We'll get to him first.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎-Understood.
‎I swear I don't know anything.
‎We operate in small cells.
‎We get invited to Telgram
‎when the higher-ups need something.
‎What's that?
‎You wouldn't know
‎even if I told you, boomer.
‎There must be a mosquito in here.
‎Or did a bitch just pinch me?
‎All right.
‎I'll pinch you.
‎No, no, no.
‎It's an anonymous group chat!
‎Like texting!
‎Are you ready to talk now?
‎Get in touch with them right now.
‎How many times do I have to tell you?
‎Unless they reach out first,
‎there's no way to contact them.
‎And they delete the chat room
‎when they're done.
‎Got it?
‎Hey, is anybody out there?
‎Come stab this bastard!
‎Stab him, damn it!
‎Hong-sik!
‎Those fucking idiots.
‎What makes you so confident?
‎The law!
‎The damn law!
‎I'm going to sue you.
‎I'll sue you for assault, torture,
‎unlawful confinement,
‎and for threatening me!
‎Your life is over.
‎The law?
‎You?
‎You see,
‎the law has nothing to do with us.
‎We're minors.
‎Don't you know what a no-charge minor is,
‎you damn boomer?
‎If you lose your parents,
‎you're an orphan.
‎If you lose your husband, you're a widow.
‎But you know,
‎there's no word for a parent
‎who loses their child.
‎The sight of their grief
‎is too wretched to name.
‎It's as if they have nothing left to lose.
‎Hey.
‎That's fake, right?
‎How can you have a gun in Korea?
‎No-charge minor, huh?
‎Nicely put.
‎I guess…
‎I'll just be a middle-aged outlaw.
‎Wait, hold on.
‎Listen, I'm not a minor.
‎I'm not underage!
‎Those guys out there are minors,
‎but I'm over 20!
‎Call an ambulance…
‎Please take me to the hospital.
‎I'm only keeping you alive
‎because I believe my daughter is.
‎If she's not,
‎you, your friends, and your family
‎will all die.
‎HEY, MIN-CHEOL
‎Hey, Min-cheol.
‎Make sure the kids keep their mouths shut.
‎Why is this bastard calling me?
‎What is it?
‎I messaged him as you told me to,
‎but he's calling.
‎He usually asks before he calls.
‎Maybe something happened.
‎Answer it.
‎Don't answer it.
‎It's the police.
‎Delete the chat room first,
‎and don't take any calls
‎from those kids for the time being.
‎Yes, sir.
‎And just to be safe,
‎get rid of that phone.
‎Yes, sir.
‎The person you are trying to reach
‎is unavailable.
‎You will be redirected to voicemail
‎after the beep, and charges will apply…
‎I took care of the girl's body.
‎UNABLE TO ACCESS CONVERSATION
‎CLOSE
‎Contact them now.
‎They deleted the chat room,
‎so we can't contact them from our end.
‎Please.
‎Contact them.
‎I swear. I seriously can't.
‎The server is overseas.
‎Please.
‎Please don't kill me!
‎HIGH SCHOOL GIRL'S BODY DISCOVERED
‎MISSING HIGH SCHOOL GIRL
‎FOUND DEAD IN THE WOODS
‎HIGH SCHOOL GIRL'S BODY
‎DISCOVERED UNDER A BRIDGE
‎This is your hair tie, right?
‎It was on the ground.
‎It's yours, right?
‎Is Hye-ri sleeping?
‎I don't know.
‎She hasn't come out of her room all day.
‎Why didn't you come out if you were awake?
‎I just got home from work.
‎How was your day, Dad?
‎You don't look so good.
‎Are you feeling sick?
‎I'm just a little tired.
‎It's because of Min-ji, isn't it?
‎No, it's not.
‎I'm really okay now.
‎Let it go, Hye-ri.
‎If you think about it,
‎she's a pitiful girl.
‎She turned out crude
‎because she grew up in a troubled home.
‎Do you happen to know
‎what her dad does for a living?
‎Why do you ask?
‎I don't know.
‎I'm just curious.
‎Hye-ri.
‎Yes?
‎From now on, don't take it lying down.
‎Make them pay several times over.
‎Don't ever let people think
‎you're an easy target.
‎Make them so afraid
‎to look you in the eye.
‎their knees buckle when they see you.
‎That way, they'll never come at you.
‎Don't worry.
‎If there's anything
‎you can't handle on your own,
‎I'll protect you.
‎Boss, I just don't get it.
‎What do you mean?
‎You know, the daughter of the chairman.
‎Why did you let her go
‎without getting paid?
‎Juhak Construction is a huge company.
‎We could've scored big, no?
‎With a little blackmail,
‎we could've sucked them dry.
‎I feel the same way too, boss.
‎I don't understand
‎why you just let her go.
‎If we make a move without thinking,
‎we'll get eaten alive.
‎-Sorry?
‎Ju Gang-chan…
‎That man will eat us alive.
‎He isn't your average guy.
‎He started as a hired thug and ended up
‎taking over construction companies.
‎My apologies, sir.
‎If you can delay construction
‎until next month,
‎we'll make sure
‎to finish demolition this month.
‎You said the same thing last time.
‎The other side brought in hired thugs, so…
‎I'm sorry, sir.
‎Are you really sorry?
‎I don't feel your sincerity.
‎That's not true, sir.
‎I truly mean it, sir.
‎What are you thinking right now?
‎Excuse me?
‎"I got down on my knees,
‎so surely he'll let it slide."
‎"I just want this to be over."
‎"If this fails after everything I've done,
‎that's on you."
‎Isn't that what you're thinking?
‎Not at all, sir.
‎I sincerely apologize.
‎Okay.
‎Then let's get a genuine apology
‎out of you.
‎He calls them bodyguards,
‎but he runs a whole organization
‎of ex-special forces mercenaries.
‎If money doesn't work,
‎then he uses violence.
‎And if that doesn't work…
‎Sir!
‎I'm sorry, sir!
‎-Please forgive me.
‎-Bow lower.
‎I'm sorry, sir!
‎Sir!
‎Man, that's insane.
‎He sounds like a total psychopath.
‎Boss.
‎Then why did you agree
‎to take care of the girl's body?
‎I already told you that I owe Chairman Ju.
‎Owe him what?
‎It's none of your business, punk.
‎You have too many questions
‎and too many cravings.
‎And too much facial hair.
‎I'll see you soon, Chairman Ju.
‎This is as far as we can go.
‎Your brother was the best operative
‎this unit has ever seen.
‎That's how 66 became the number
‎that symbolizes
‎the Republic's finest warrior.
‎But during a mission,
‎some rat-bastard stabbed him in the back
‎and got him killed.
‎That rat-bastard traitor
‎killed all of his comrades,
‎stole the number 66 from your brother,
‎and became a lapdog for the South!
‎I'm giving you number 66,
‎the number that belonged to your brother.
‎Go to the South and bring me back
‎the head of the fake Number 66.
‎I couldn't locate the target.
‎Here.
‎This is the police station
‎where the guy he was with is being held.
‎One more thing.
‎The thing is,
‎our operational funds were cut off
‎a long time ago,
‎so our comrades here are struggling.
‎When you finish the mission and head back,
‎please ask them to replenish the funds.
‎Comrade.
‎I think you've been in the South too long.
‎Oh, well…
‎Here's the car key.
‎42 MYEONGUN-RO, DOWON-GU, SEOUL
‎DOWON POLICE STATION
‎How can he sleep in a situation like this?
‎That beast.
‎Why do I have to suffer
‎because of that wild boar?
‎If I ever talk to Park Jin-cheol again,
‎I'm no better than an animal.
‎It's just my imagination.
‎I'm imagining things because of that jerk.
‎When will I get out?
‎I'm hungry.
‎Da-bin…
‎Excuse me.
‎Can I get something to eat?
‎Come on, shouldn't you at least feed us?
‎I know we're in lockup,
‎but police officers in this country
‎should bring us food when…
‎Oh, it's here?
‎Here it is.
‎Salute. Thank you for your hard work.
‎Sir, can you tell me
‎what's on today's menu?
‎Are you Park Jin-cheol?
‎Well, that came out of nowhere.
‎Your clothes look big on you.
‎You should've found someone your size.
‎Don't make this hard. Where's 66?
‎Did you say 66?
‎What's that?
‎-The South's most elite operative.
‎-Oh.
‎Did you come from the North?
‎You've come to the right place.
‎It's me.
‎You're funny.
‎-You're not 66.
‎-Come on.
‎I can wear a size 66, or medium,
‎if I lose weight.
‎Now, where have I seen him?
‎Oh.
‎Is it this person?
‎You bastard.
‎I'll ask you one last time.
‎Where's 66?
‎Hey, now.
‎This isn't fair. There are civilians here.
‎Hold on a second.
‎789-9, Mangyun-dong.
‎Second floor above Dowon Laundry.
‎That's his address. Satisfied now?
‎You're softer than you look.
‎I look soft too, man.
‎Then again,
‎maybe it's better
‎to die sooner than later.
‎Okay.
‎I'll kill him quickly for your sake.
‎No.
‎I meant that you'll die.
‎You son of a bitch.
‎What's taking so long? Is there a problem?
‎I'll see you again.
‎Excuse me.
‎Hey.
‎Excuse me. Hey.
‎Excuse me!
‎-Sir, I'm sorry.
‎-What the hell?
‎I'm really sorry.
‎What's the matter with you?
‎Is anyone there?
‎Someone's dying in here!
‎He's dying!
‎What's wrong?
‎Hurry!
‎He can't breathe!
‎He can't breathe. Keep still.
‎CPR! Stay still!
‎Stay put! Hurry!
‎Please hurry!
‎Oh my goodness!
‎What's the matter with you?
‎Just wait here for a bit!
‎Open this right now!
‎I'm really sorry. I'll be right back.
‎What?
‎Hey!
‎Come on, I'm getting tired!
‎Just die!
‎Hey, that's enough!
‎You might kill him.
‎Come on, sir.
‎Our construction project
‎is about to fall through because of you.
‎We gave you plenty of chances to leave.
‎I'll… I'll move out.
‎Let's get ready.
‎Are you saying you killed this student?
‎Tell me.
‎You can take care of the body, right?
‎You're scaring me.
‎Why are you asking me this?
‎Money isn't a problem.
‎I'll give you as much as you want.
‎No, forget it!
‎I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
‎Go away!
‎Wow, this editing is incredible.
‎I'm not a bad actor.
‎Maybe I should go into acting.
‎Boss, I got his signature.
‎I'm tired of this line of work.
‎I need to quit and retire.
‎Don't you agree?
‎Where did you get the gun?
‎EVIDENCE ITEM NO. 9
‎EVIDENCE ITEM NO. 10: MOBILE PHONE
‎-Goodbye, sir.
‎-Good work today.
‎INTERROGATION ROOM
‎Is he still refusing to talk?
‎Yes, sir. Not a single word.
‎Hey, mister. Your hearing is fine, right?
‎You think cops are going to be nice
‎just because the world's a better place?
‎What's your name?
‎-Don't you know your own name?
‎-Look!
‎This has been going on all night!
‎-If you refuse to--
‎-Forget it.
‎Just get his prints and check.
‎Look him up in the system.
‎Okay, sir.
‎Your prints, please.
‎-Open the trunk.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎Damn it, it smells like blood.
‎It's a dead body!
‎You should've at least
‎covered it with plastic, idiot!
‎-I'm sorry, sir!
‎-Hey, kid.
‎Bring a sack.
‎You idiot.
‎Are you dodging?
‎Oh, yeah?
‎REQUESTING FINGERPRINT CHECK
‎There are always people
‎who make you go through so much trouble.
‎Back in my day,
‎we'd take people like him and just…
‎For goodness' sake.
‎Wait, what?
‎-Captain.
‎-What is it?
‎ACCESS APPROVAL CODE REQUIRED
‎"Access denied"?
‎I'll try it again.
‎Does that belong to him?
‎Yes, sir. We confiscated it.
‎"My daughter"?
‎What the hell?
‎Hello?
‎Is that you, Min-ji?
‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎Min-ji…
‎I'm sorry for bringing you into this.
‎Some guy from the North came to kill you.
‎Rock and roll!
‎Min-ji will be in danger too.
‎Hurry up.
‎Let's go find Min-ji.
‎Get rid of any evidence first.
‎Kim is out of his mind right now,
‎looking for his daughter.
‎Where did you get that phone?
‎It's the girl
‎I messed around with last night.
‎Look for Kim's daughter right now.
‎We need to take her hostage first.
‎Subtitle translation by: Jenny Kim