‪AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‪EPISODE 1
‪Are you kidding me right now?
‪Move your car! It's blocking the road!
‪Goodness gracious.
‪Jeez, just walk if you're in a rush.
‪I'm starving. When will the food be ready?
‪I know. It's taking so long.
‪When is our food going to be ready?
‪You're drunk!
‪What was that?
‪Damn it. What the hell?
‪Hey, you. Come here.
‪Damn it, it's broken.
‪Goddamn it. Come here.
‪Hey, I said come here!
‪Where the hell are you going?
‪Hey!
‪Who do you think you are?
‪Are you pulling
‪an insurance scam or something?
‪If you bump into someone's car,
‪you should be down on your knees
‪begging for forgiveness.
‪This needs to be replaced entirely.
‪I wonder how much it'll cost.
‪I think my arm is okay,
‪so you can just go.
‪Man, you're unbelievable.
‪I'm really okay, so you can leave.
‪Are you serious right now?
‪Have you lost your damn mind?
‪Do you have a death wish?
‪What?
‪What are you looking at?
‪I'm sorry.
‪I apologize.
‪It's too late for that.
‪Try running your mouth again.
‪Come on, let's get going. We're late.
‪Let's go.
‪Go on, then.
‪I'll accept your apology.
‪Let's call it even with this.
‪Wow, have you been working out these days?
‪-That was a nice punch.
‪-Is he dead?
‪-Should we cover him with a blanket?
‪-Goddamn it!
‪AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‪Good morning!
‪I think you're missing a button.
‪-I don't think so.
‪-Are you sure?
‪Let me sweep this for you.
‪No, it's okay.
‪-Let me do it for you.
‪-Thank you.
‪YOUR CHILD'S REBELLIOUS PHASE
‪KIM MIN-JI
‪RESTRICTED AREA
‪Min-ji, wake up.
‪ENTER WITHOUT PERMISSION AND YOU'LL DIE!
‪Min-ji.
‪Kim Min-ji, you're late!
‪-It's time for break--
‪-Enough about breakfast!
‪Does anyone give you crap
‪if I skip breakfast?
‪Don't smile!
‪You're a student,
‪so you need a solid meal before school.
‪Kim Min-ji!
‪SCHOOL NOTICE
‪EMERGENCY CONTACT FORM
‪MOTHER: X
‪SIBLINGS: X
‪Hey, Min-ji.
‪I need the name of a close friend
‪and their phone number.
‪Kim Min-ji!
‪Kang Hye-ryeong.
‪Her number is 010-0610-6003.
‪I filled out the form.
‪Have some breakfast.
‪I'm late.
‪-Your report card…
‪-Don't look at that!
‪-Level eight? What happened?
‪-The higher the number, the better.
‪-Right?
‪-The rules have changed.
‪I told you before.
‪-Take it easy on the studying.
‪-Okay.
‪Kang…
‪Hye…
‪ryeong.
‪LAUNDRY
‪Min-ji!
‪-Hello.
‪-Hey.
‪How's your father doing?
‪-What do you mean?
‪-Well, the thugs…
‪Never mind.
‪By the way,
‪why don't you alter your uniform?
‪I'm an expert at altering, you know.
‪It's okay. I never know
‪when I'll be transferring again.
‪That's my bus.
‪What?
‪Have a good day.
‪Gosh, her uniform
‪is always perfectly pressed.
‪Mr. Kim!
‪Are you okay?
‪You seem okay.
‪I saw those thugs
‪provoking you that night.
‪I'm sorry I couldn't step in.
‪I'm quite the scaredy-cat, you see.
‪I would've done the same in your shoes.
‪Goodness, Mr. Kim.
‪You should really press your suit.
‪That's what a dry cleaner is for.
‪Come on, you live right above one.
‪That just hurts my pride.
‪I'll drop it off next time.
‪I'll press this for you in a jiffy.
‪Let's go inside.
‪-Come on.
‪-I have to catch the bus.
‪Let me press it for you.
‪Wait.
‪Mr. Kim.
‪Mr. Kim!
‪Jeez. Like father, like daughter.
‪They're exactly the same.
‪My sales pitch never works on them.
‪Wait!
‪Thank you.
‪Sorry, coming through.
‪Don't push!
‪Don't run. You'll get hurt.
‪SCHOOL VIOLENCE
‪DON'T STAND BY, PROTECT VICTIMS!
‪-Did you have breakfast?
‪-Yes, sir.
‪-Good morning, sir.
‪-Hey.
‪-You need to say hello like this.
‪-You're right.
‪SANGSAENG SAVINGS BANK
‪Hello, Manager Kim.
‪You're first as always.
‪Hello.
‪SAVINGS BANK
‪LOAN APPLICATIONS & INQUIRIES
‪Customer number 155, please.
‪CORPORATE CARD CHARGES
‪SEOREUNG CO., LTD. / CHINESE FOOD
‪REQUESTER: KANG HAK-SU
‪DIVISION: TREASURY
‪LEAVE REQUEST HISTORY
‪I've taken a look at your assets, and…
‪Sir.
‪What is it?
‪These are the corporate card charges.
‪You charged 95,000 won for Chinese food
‪the Wednesday before last.
‪So?
‪You were on leave that day
‪for your wedding anniversary.
‪The receipt is missing as well,
‪so maybe there was an oversight?
‪Kim, do you eat a lot of fish
‪for brain food?
‪Excuse me?
‪How is your memory so good?
‪Oh, well, I do try to eat a lot of fish.
‪I like mackerel in particular.
‪Stop eating mackerel and saury
‪and learn how to bend the rules instead.
‪Be flexible.
‪Just write it off
‪as a company dinner expense.
‪Yes, sir.
‪I'll write it off
‪as a company dinner expense.
‪Thank you so much
‪for remembering my wedding anniversary.
‪No problem.
‪Jeez, he's so frustrating.
‪PLEASE USE THE NEXT COUNTER
‪Let's call it even with this.
‪SELF-DEFENSE ITEMS
‪I have to pre-order and stand in line
‪just to get some dessert?
‪What time does this start?
‪-Mr. Kim.
‪-Jeez, you scared me!
‪What is it, Sang-a?
‪Is something wrong?
‪Why are you looking up self-defense items?
‪Oh, it's nothing.
‪Wait, are you going to use it at night…
‪on Mr. Kang?
‪Mr. Kang?
‪Of course not.
‪It's not that.
‪My neighborhood feels unsafe these days.
‪Hey, Sang-a.
‪This looks useful, right?
‪It's easy to carry around
‪and seems effective.
‪Is it for you?
‪I think it's for women.
‪Min-ji's birthday is coming up.
‪Oh, it's your daughter's birthday.
‪How old is she?
‪She's a high school junior.
‪A self-defense item
‪for a high school girl…
‪Why don't you just ask her what she wants?
‪I'd like to,
‪but she won't talk to me these days.
‪She just avoids me.
‪Sounds like she's going through
‪a late rebellious phase.
‪Don't worry so much.
‪They're all like that at that age.
‪Maybe things might be better
‪if her mom was around.
‪I'll help you choose a gift.
‪-Really?
‪-I'm going to the department store anyway.
‪Let's go together after work.
‪No, you don't have to do--
‪We'll leave at six o'clock sharp.
‪Hey, Kim Min-ji.
‪Min-ji.
‪Lend me your gym clothes.
‪Hye-ryeong, you didn't return them
‪the last time, so I had to track you down.
‪Come on, we're friends. I'm begging you.
‪What's this?
‪Thank you. I'll bring it right back.
‪Jeez, wash your clothes.
‪Hey, Ju Hye-ri, what's this?
‪My dad got it for me on his business trip.
‪It's so pretty.
‪-I've never seen this from this brand.
‪-Me neither.
‪It's not available in Korea.
‪It's limited edition.
‪Mine's just cheap fast-fashion.
‪I'm so jealous, Hye-ri.
‪Yeah, yours looks cheap.
‪Does it really?
‪-How much was it?
‪-It was 5,000 won.
‪What's with her?
‪Has she lost her mind?
‪Forget it.
‪Leave her alone.
‪You'll get that old widower reek on you.
‪Hey, it's Kim Nam-hoon.
‪He's not even trying to hide
‪that he's here to see Hye-ri.
‪Hye-ri, do you have a minute?
‪Hey, dude.
‪WOMEN
‪Hey, what flavor was that again?
‪Grape.
‪-Can I try it?
‪-No.
‪-Come on, let me hit it once.
‪-Smoke your own.
‪Okay, okay.
‪-One more puff.
‪-No.
‪-Let's swap.
‪-Come on, just for a day.
‪-I said no. I like this flavor.
‪Hey.
‪Damn, it reeks like an old widower here.
‪The cigarette smell on you is worse.
‪What did you just say?
‪I asked you a question.
‪Don't look at me like that.
‪I said don't look at me like that!
‪Hey!
‪That's enough.
‪Stop picking on that pathetic kid.
‪Why am I pathetic?
‪I mean, just look at you.
‪You're pathetic.
‪SANGSAENG SAVINGS BANK
‪Mr. Kim!
‪-Hi, Sang-a.
‪-Let's go get your daughter's gift.
‪Did you mean it earlier?
‪Seriously? I'm hurt.
‪I mean, are you sure?
‪I don't want to be a nuisance.
‪If you don't want to, then no worries.
‪Goodbye.
‪Sang-a!
‪Wait.
‪Sang-a.
‪There it is.
‪PRE-ORDER LINE
‪-What the heck?
‪-Mr. Kim.
‪What's this?
‪-Give me your credit card.
‪-My credit card?
‪It'll only take longer if we go together.
‪You can wait in line here
‪while I buy your daughter's gift.
‪It's a win-win situation.
‪I texted you a screenshot
‪of my pre-order DM,
‪so you just have to pick it up
‪when it's your turn.
‪A screenshot?
‪Hold on.
‪I can't view photos on my phone.
‪How many zeros is this?
‪What? 500,000 won?
‪Next in line, please.
‪Oh, right.
‪I need to confirm your pre-order.
‪It's under Jung Sang-a.
‪Not the name.
‪I need to see the pre-order DM.
‪What's a DM?
‪If your pre-order isn't confirmed,
‪you'll have to move to the walk-in line.
‪WALK-IN LINE
‪But she said she pre-ordered--
‪-Next in line, please.
‪-Jeez, come on.
‪Here.
‪Okay, you're all set.
‪Thank you.
‪Come on, Mr. Kim.
‪It's your daughter's birthday.
‪I'm sorry, but I'd like a refund.
‪Just a minute, please.
‪I stay on top of current trends, you know.
‪This is the trend these days.
‪Just trust me and buy it.
‪My daughter is in high school.
‪It makes no sense for a high schooler
‪to wear a T-shirt that costs 500,000 won.
‪-Refund, please.
‪-Yes, it's expensive.
‪But this is the secret weapon
‪to get through her rebellious phase.
‪Imagine the worst-case scenario.
‪"Worst-case"?
‪"As my dad,
‪what have you ever done for me?"
‪If she says that, it'll be the end
‪of your father-daughter relationship.
‪You need to do something big
‪to prepare for the worst-case scenario
‪and say something back to her.
‪"I bought you a 500,000 won T-shirt!"
‪Something like that.
‪This is super popular
‪among kids these days.
‪She'll think, "My out-of-touch dad
‪is actually pretty cool."
‪I bet she'll look at you differently.
‪Min-ji, I'm home.
‪When did you get home?
‪What are you doing?
‪Kim Min-ji.
‪I'm talking to you.
‪Don't wash your clothes with mine anymore.
‪They make mine smell like an old man.
‪All right.
‪Then from now on,
‪do your own laundry.
‪JU HYE-RI
‪PEOPLE TAGGED IN THIS PHOTO
‪KIM NAM-HOON
‪Wait, why can't I unlike this?
‪Who are you?
‪Oh gosh.
‪Dad.
‪Go to sleep in your room.
‪What is it, Min-ji?
‪I said go to sleep in your room.
‪Right.
‪Dad.
‪Yeah?
‪About what I said earlier…
‪I forgot to do the dishes.
‪You can do it in the morning.
‪Just go sleep.
‪Okay. You should go to bed too.
‪Good morning!
‪I think you're missing a button.
‪You sure it's okay?
‪DOWON LAUNDRY
‪What's gotten into her?
‪All right, then.
‪I'll make Min-ji's favorite.
‪Soy sauce egg rice.
‪-Hey!
‪-I need my gym clothes.
‪Did you see the look on her face?
‪-Hye-ryeong, wake up.
‪-What is it?
‪I have PE next period.
‪Where are my gym clothes?
‪I gave them back to you.
‪When? I never got them.
‪I left them on your desk.
‪Hurry up.
‪Hey, Min-ji.
‪Check the trash can.
‪KIM MIN-JI
‪Did you see the look on her face?
‪I just played volleyball,
‪so it'll smell like sweat.
‪What?
‪Five-on-five match in ten minutes!
‪The losing team will clean for a month.
‪Min-ji.
‪Kim Min-ji, come here.
‪Why are you only wearing
‪half of your gym clothes?
‪Are you going to play basketball
‪in a skirt?
‪-I forgot.
‪-"Kim Nam-hoon"?
‪Nam-hoon didn't lend you his pants?
‪All right, double punch! One!
‪-Taekwon!
‪Two!
‪Now, triple punch! One!
‪-Taekwondo!
‪Two!
‪Back to ready!
‪Kicking stance, ready!
‪One!
‪Two!
‪Proper mind!
‪Nice!
‪Proper body! Nice.
‪Proper posture!
‪Proper…
‪Whatever!
‪I wasn't done.
‪That's it for today.
‪Let's go play!
‪Come on.
‪It's okay.
‪My goodness.
‪I can't tell if this is a Taekwondo studio
‪or a daycare center.
‪Jin-cheol, why would you…
‪Jeez, Jin-cheol.
‪What's the matter with you?
‪Jin-cheol!
‪Hey.
‪Who asked that person to help out?
‪No one did.
‪Let's cross the road!
‪Come on, kids. Let's cross now!
‪-You can cross the road.
‪-Go slowly.
‪Cross the road, kids!
‪I said cross the road!
‪Go ahead. What's wrong?
‪Why aren't you crossing?
‪-Mommy, I'm scared!
‪-Are you scared of the cars?
‪Goodness, let me help you.
‪-Here we go.
‪-Let's go!
‪All right.
‪Oh my!
‪My goodness, sir!
‪Where are you going?
‪Over there?
‪Got it! All right.
‪-Let's go!
‪-Wait!
‪-Is he stealing the cart?
‪-Surely not. He's probably just helping.
‪I have to go this way!
‪No!
‪It's this way!
‪How wonderful is it
‪to be needed
‪and to help others?
‪In these dark and rough times,
‪I will be a positive force
‪and a guiding light.
‪You did well today, Park Jin-cheol.
‪KOREAN MARINE VETERANS FEDERATION
‪Copy that. Start operation.
‪Unit 911, fall back. I'm taking the lead.
‪Grenade out.
‪Out of the way. That's it!
‪Get out of the way. That's it.
‪Act like true Marines!
‪Grenade out! Fall back!
‪Bomb!
‪PURE TAEKWONDO
‪Retreat! Fall back!
‪Don't come out! Move aside!
‪Hey! Didn't you hear what I just said?
‪Get them!
‪I'll do it!
‪Oh, damn it.
‪Hold on.
‪Did you hear something?
‪Don't make any footsteps.
‪What's that noise? A bomb. It's a bomb!
‪Hey.
‪You were in here?
‪Man, all I did was kick in a door,
‪and now my leg hurts.
‪Gosh, it hurts.
‪What are you looking at?
‪Why aren't you greeting your senior?
‪You crazy little…
‪Don't you know how to knock?
‪Why did you kick my office door
‪like a donkey?
‪Is this my doorknob?
‪I did knock, 12 times.
‪You didn't hear me because of your game.
‪A Taekwondo master like you
‪should have better manners.
‪Jeez!
‪Everybody, fall in.
‪What are you, a kid?
‪This is an important battle, okay?
‪You want to end up like that door?
‪Kim should be getting off work now.
‪Hurry up and go before I smash that.
‪What does him getting off work
‪have to do with me?
‪Today's the one day out of the year
‪we get together!
‪That's today?
‪Seriously, it's today?
‪Oh man.
‪I must be getting old.
‪It slipped my mind.
‪Come on. Let's go see how much he's aged.
‪Goodness gracious.
‪Hey, what are you going to do about this?
‪Huh?
‪Just stick it back in.
‪"Just stick it back in"?
‪I can just stick it in?
‪All right.
‪It's nice and cold. Drink up.
‪Yeah, give me soju.
‪Right here.
‪That white Taekwondo uniform
‪is getting on my damn nerves.
‪It's embarrassing.
‪Go sit over there alone.
‪I came straight here
‪after dropping the kids off.
‪Don't flip the meat yet.
‪You're one to talk.
‪Take a look at yourself.
‪Are you going on a mission after you eat?
‪Hey, what's wrong with this?
‪You embarrassed?
‪Who looks more ridiculous
‪between the two of us?
‪I just need to take off my jacket.
‪Wow.
‪Look, it's Da-bin. Say hello.
‪-Hi.
‪I wear this because I miss my daughter.
‪She's out and about all the time,
‪so I never get to see her.
‪But if I look in the mirror, I can say,
‪"Hey, look who it is.
‪It's my daughter, Da-bin!"
‪"It's me, your dad. Good to see you."
‪"So, are you coming home today?"
‪Da-bin seems embarrassed by you.
‪She can't hold her head up.
‪Let me help her with that.
‪Hey.
‪You're reminding me of the door.
‪Do you need me
‪to put you in your place again?
‪The meat is burning.
‪You're ridiculous.
‪No answer or anything. He just walks by.
‪-Seriously?
‪-Here.
‪-All right, all right.
‪-Let's drink.
‪-Cheers.
‪I wonder who Tae-hun takes after
‪to be so rude.
‪-You.
‪Right, I'm rude.
‪These drinks taste bittersweet tonight.
‪But you know what?
‪Raising Da-bin is what keeps me going.
‪You know, I may not be as strong
‪or as successful as before,
‪but I like my life right now.
‪-You punk.
‪-But I have to say,
‪Da-bin grew up too quickly.
‪She was such a cute little baby,
‪but now that she's in high school,
‪she refuses to listen to me.
‪Soon enough, she'll meet someone
‪and get married, right?
‪And we'll grow further apart, right?
‪That just…
‪Just thinking about it breaks my heart.
‪Da-bin.
‪Please don't leave me.
‪You're not a fool for your daughter.
‪You're just a fool.
‪I have to go.
‪-Already?
‪Min-ji's alone.
‪Hey, she might not like it
‪if you always rush home early.
‪Don't drink too much and go home.
‪-What's this?
‪-Give it to your kids.
‪-Jeez, come on.
‪-You shouldn't have.
‪-Hey, hold on.
‪-Wait a minute.
‪Just sit down for a bit. Two more minutes.
‪Don't be so cold.
‪You didn't have to.
‪Hey, Da-bin.
‪Your uncle gave you pocket money.
‪-Listen, Kim.
‪-You should thank him.
‪Let's see each other more often, okay?
‪Seriously, once a year? That's ridiculous.
‪If we meet once a year,
‪-that's only 35 more times at best.
‪-That's true.
‪I understand the decision you made
‪after your wife passed away,
‪but you need to live your own life too.
‪When will you stop making your daughter
‪the sole focus of your life?
‪-Min-ji's grown up now.
‪-He's right.
‪She'll have a boyfriend soon too.
‪She's still a kid.
‪The more you hover over your kids,
‪the more suffocated they'll feel.
‪Stop being so damn annoying!
‪Come on, can't we have a quiet meal?
‪He's pissing me off!
‪-Can you just put out your cigarette?
‪-Why?
‪This is a terrace!
‪Why do I have to put it out?
‪There are other customers here.
‪What other customers? Who?
‪Who?
‪-Stop staring.
‪-What are you looking at?
‪What? You pissed off?
‪He must be really pissed.
‪What?
‪Don't. This has nothing to do with us.
‪We're middle-aged men
‪who tolerate injustice.
‪We're no longer young.
‪We're just middle-aged men with glasses.
‪Right?
‪We already paid, so let's go.
‪Come on.
‪Get up.
‪Hey, grunt! Where are you going?
‪-Enough already.
‪-Let go of me.
‪You off to scrub the slop bucket?
‪Jin-cheol. You remember, right?
‪Right.
‪We're just middle-aged men with glasses.
‪What? You scared?
‪You were glaring at me earlier.
‪Get over here, you asshole!
‪Hey, grunt. Why don't you do some drills?
‪Come on, give me 20 reps.
‪One, two!
‪What's that?
‪This is embarrassing. Who's this?
‪She's pretty!
‪How cute.
‪Why don't you introduce me to her?
‪I'll treat her really well.
‪Rock and roll!
‪Jin-cheol.
‪What the hell?
‪You fat pig!
‪Hey, pig, get up.
‪Let me borrow your bag.
‪Kim, shouldn't we stop him?
‪Where did he go?
‪Did you see a tall guy with glasses
‪in a depressing black suit?
‪A tall guy.
‪Hey, Kim…
‪Fine, just go.
‪Is this the police?
‪There's a fight going on right now.
‪Yes, a serious fight. Someone might die.
‪Please hurry!
‪No, no. You're dead if you use that.
‪No, don't do that.
‪He should run. Is he frozen or something?
‪Stop.
‪Stop!
‪Officer, shoot something!
‪-Shoot your gun!
‪-Gun?
‪Shoot something! Anything! Hurry!
‪Hurry!
‪Whose jacket is this? "Kim Nam-hoon"?
‪-What are you doing?
‪-Who's Kim Nam-hoon?
‪I don't know.
‪What's the matter with you?
‪Have a good day.
‪Min-ji's grown up now.
‪He's right.
‪She'll have a boyfriend soon too.
‪Does she have a boyfriend?
‪Hey.
‪Do you know where Kim Nam-hoon is?
‪I'm not sure.
‪I need to give this back.
‪-You could've left it on my desk.
‪-What?
‪You were looking for me, right?
‪Oh, I just wanted to thank you.
‪-That's it?
‪-Well…
‪I can give you this.
‪Really? Strawberry milk?
‪What am I, a kid?
‪You're the one who liked my post, right?
‪What?
‪I'm not on social media.
‪Oh, yeah?
‪Then what's this?
‪KIM NAM-HOON
‪I can DM you, right?
‪Yeah.
‪Never mind. You should DM me first.
‪Hey.
‪But you have to DM me back.
‪I'll think about it.
‪-Why? What's there to think about?
‪-What?
‪Why can't I think about it?
‪You can't do that.
‪You told me to DM you first.
‪Come out. Hye-ri wants to see you.
‪Get up.
‪You know why I hit you, right?
‪Hye-ri asked you a question. Answer her.
‪You still don't know?
‪You hit on Hye-ri's boyfriend,
‪you sly bitch.
‪I never did that.
‪All I did was return his gym clothes.
‪Why did you borrow them
‪in the first place?
‪Who do you think you are?
‪Why didn't you wear
‪your own goddamn gym clothes?
‪Because you guys threw them in the trash.
‪Don't worry.
‪I have no reason to contact him.
‪I don't want anything to do with you.
‪Hey, it seems like you're mistaken.
‪I'm not pissed
‪because you tried to take my toy.
‪It's because of your stench.
‪I'm pissed because it'll rub off on him.
‪She has no idea.
‪Grab her.
‪Get up.
‪How do I describe this smell?
‪It's like a cheap suit
‪shoved in the back of a closet…
‪Oh, I know.
‪It's the smell of a motherless child.
‪Hey.
‪-You think you know me?!
‪-You crazy bitch!
‪Who do you think you are?!
‪Who do you think you are? Huh?!
‪-Hye-ri, are you okay?
‪-Who the hell do you think you are?!
‪Hey!
‪You think you know me so well?!
‪-What the hell do you know?!
‪-Get off her!
‪-Get off her already!
‪-Stop!
‪It wasn't just a fight.
‪It was an assault, Mr. Kim.
‪Min-ji just attacked her.
‪I'll be right there.
‪Please hurry.
‪I'm about to lose my job.
‪Why did it have to be Hye-ri?
‪The victim's father is the chairman
‪of Juhak Construction.
‪You've heard of them, right?
‪You built this hotel as well,
‪didn't you, Chairman Ju?
‪Yes.
‪My daughter had graduated
‪from elementary school,
‪so it was about four years ago.
‪Oh, you have a daughter.
‪She must be pretty if she takes after you.
‪You're too kind.
‪Anyway, this is the first time
‪I've had a meeting in a spa.
‪There's no need to watch what we say
‪or hide anything here.
‪All right, then.
‪Let me ask you point-blank.
‪What's in it for me
‪if this redevelopment plan goes through?
‪It'll provide a better living environment
‪for your constituents.
‪And?
‪It'll create
‪a much more favorable environment
‪for your political fundraising.
‪Twice as much as last time.
‪All right. Let's do this together.
‪There must be something in the water.
‪I feel refreshed to my very core.
‪I should get going now.
‪Please take your time.
‪Goodness, Chairman Ju.
‪What happened to your body?
‪Oh, it's not a pretty sight, is it?
‪I got some tattoos on a whim
‪when I was younger,
‪but I regretted them
‪after I started my business.
‪I was ashamed to show my daughter too.
‪So I just burned them off myself
‪with a torch.
‪With a torch?
‪Why didn't you go to a hospital?
‪I guess it was a pledge
‪not to go back to my old life.
‪But still, it must've been very painful.
‪It was nothing compared to what I've done
‪to make it this far.
‪It was more painful…
‪for those who didn't keep
‪their promises with me
‪and disappeared as a result.
‪I'm counting on you, Assemblyman Sim.
‪Right, yes, of course.
‪Sir, your wife is calling.
‪-What is it?
‪-Honey, something terrible happened.
‪Hye-ri…
‪Hye-ri was assaulted by someone at school!
‪Okay.
‪Let's go to Hye-ri's school.
‪Yes, sir.
‪You can't go in.
‪The chairman asked me to come, asshole.
‪Hey, Nam.
‪What's the matter with them?
‪Be quiet.
‪The chairman is inside.
‪You told me to come.
‪So I came.
‪There's been a change of plans.
‪I'll get back to you.
‪Am I some lapdog
‪you can just order around?
‪I thought you knew already.
‪No, I didn't.
‪I didn't know that.
‪This lapdog is leaving.
‪Goddamn it.
‪When in the world is he arriving?
‪Let's go, Hye-ri.
‪How dare he make us wait?
‪Sit down.
‪We should at least talk to him.
‪What took you so long?
‪How on earth did you raise your child
‪for her to act this way?
‪Just look at my child!
‪How can I send her to school now?
‪Why won't you look at her?
‪Take a good look at her!
‪I'm sorry.
‪I've only heard about
‪school violence and bullies.
‪I had no idea Hye-ri was in the same class
‪as someone like her!
‪Dad, I didn't do anything wrong.
‪She and her girls kept harassing me.
‪I took it for as long as I could
‪before fighting back!
‪Kim Min-ji.
‪Be quiet.
‪But she hit me first!
‪Don't you believe me?
‪Min-ji.
‪Mr. Kim, I think you should
‪come to an agreement with the victim.
‪No, forget it.
‪I demand a disciplinary hearing,
‪and I want this on her record.
‪Dad!
‪Don't you have any pride at all?
‪I'm sorry.
‪I've fallen short as a parent
‪since I'm raising her alone.
‪As a fellow parent raising a daughter,
‪I ask that you find it in your heart
‪to forgive us.
‪I'll take responsibility as her father,
‪and have her transferred.
‪Dad!
‪As a fellow parent raising a daughter,
‪you say?
‪Right.
‪It's not easy raising a daughter.
‪Especially on your own.
‪It must've been hard
‪growing up without a mother.
‪It's natural for kids to fight
‪while growing up.
‪We received an apology,
‪so let's settle this matter
‪with her transferring.
‪-Dad!
‪-Honey!
‪We'll leave it at this.
‪Thank you.
‪Min-ji.
‪Kim Min-ji.
‪KIM NAM-HOON
‪What does her father do?
‪I believe he's an ordinary office worker.
‪Thank you for your leniency, Chairman Ju.
‪Thank you. This will never happen again.
‪Of course.
‪Because if something like this
‪happens again,
‪this school and all of you will disappear.
‪Min-ji.
‪Are you hungry?
‪Should we go eat?
‪Min-ji.
‪Kim Min-ji.
‪Why won't you believe me?
‪Of course, I believe you.
‪Then why do I have to transfer?
‪I didn't do anything wrong.
‪Why did you have to grovel and kneel?
‪Is it because Hye-ri's dad
‪is a powerful man?
‪I'm so ashamed.
‪I feel so angry, frustrated, and pathetic.
‪What have you done with your life?
‪Her dad's a rich chairman
‪with lots of connections,
‪but why are you a lowly office worker?
‪Why did you even have me?
‪Min-ji.
‪As my dad…
‪As my dad, you mean the world to me.
‪I don't have a mom.
‪You're all I have left,
‪but if you're not on my side…
‪They're the bad ones.
‪You, of all people, should've believed me.
‪Let's go home.
‪I don't want to be with you.
‪I'm staying at Hye-ryeong's tonight,
‪so don't call me.
‪If you do,
‪I'll run away from home.
‪Min-ji.
‪It's your birthday tomorrow.
‪Kim Min-ji!
‪I hate my birthday.
‪It's the day Mom died.
‪THE LATE IM YU-JIN
‪These flowers are my favorite.
‪They're called honeysuckles.
‪The meaning behind them is pretty too.
‪Do you know what it is?
‪What is it?
‪Love and…
‪-‪devotion.
‪-Devotion.
‪I'm sorry, Yu-jin.
‪I have something to tell you.
‪I'll be at the back gate at school.
‪I'll wait until you get here.
‪DAD
‪The person you are trying to reach
‪is unavailable. You will be redirected…
‪I don't want to be with you.
‪I'm staying at Hye-ryeong's tonight,
‪so don't call me.
‪If you do,
‪I'll run away from home.
‪The phone you are calling is turned off.
‪You will be redirected to voicemail.
‪Hello?
‪Is this Kang Hye-ryeong?
‪Yes. Who is this?
‪I'm Min-ji's dad.
‪What? How did you know my number?
‪Min-ji told me.
‪Hye-ryeong, by any chance,
‪were you with Min-ji last night?
‪No.
‪Then have you heard from her at all?
‪I'm hanging up now.
‪Hey, I'm Min-ji's dad.
‪Have you seen her?
‪No, she hasn't come to school yet.
‪Kim Nam-hoon?
‪Did you meet Min-ji yesterday?
‪I didn't send her that DM.
‪hey were these thugs…
‪I only heard something
‪about the back gate.
‪I'm sorry.
‪I couldn't do anything
‪because they took my phone.
‪How on earth did you raise your child
‪for her to act this way?
‪We just have to act like
‪we don't know anything.
‪I told everyone to keep quiet,
‪so don't worry.
‪-But you never know.
‪-Just trust me.
‪You know I'm not some low-life thug.
‪Hey, it's all clean now.
‪See? Even the weather is on our side.
‪If someone reported it,
‪the cops would be here already.
‪Nobody will find her.
‪And you said her dad's a loser, right?
‪-Can I ask a question?
‪-Damn it, you scared me!
‪I'm Min-ji's dad.
‪We don't know where she is,
‪so just go on your way.
‪I never said I was looking for her.
‪This is your hair tie, right?
‪It was on the ground.
‪I said go on your way
‪unless you want your ass kicked!
‪-It's yours, right?
‪-Goddamn it.
‪Look at you.
‪-You're dead meat.
‪-I'll ask you one last time.
‪-Where's Min-ji?
‪-Hey, old man.
‪What do you think?
‪Huh?
‪Is it clocking to you that you're screwed?
‪Who the hell do you think you are?
‪You think you're special?
‪Show me, then.
‪Take off your clothes and fight.
‪Want me to take it off for you?
‪Let me go!
‪Put down the gun.
‪Let me go.
‪Discharge me right now!
‪You can't discharge him.
‪You know as well as I do, sir.
‪No one can ever know he exists.
‪Codename 66.
‪A North Korean operative who defected
‪and was recruited
‪by South Korean intelligence.
‪He acted as a double agent
‪on five occasions
‪and has been credited with
‪17 infiltration missions in the North.
‪He led the assassination operation
‪targeting North Korea's supreme commander,
‪prompting China and Russia
‪to assign teams to track him.
‪What the hell?
‪Discharging someone like him
‪is unthinkable.
‪If the North finds out he's still alive,
‪his existence alone…
‪will cause a diplomatic crisis.
‪Tell me.
‪Where's Min-ji?
‪AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‪-The law?
‪-Who the hell are you?
‪I guess…
‪I'll just be a middle-aged outlaw.
‪The government denies
‪Agent Kim's existence.
‪Arm the infiltration team.
‪Hey, mister!
‪Is that bastard sleeping right now?
‪In this situation?
‪I'm only keeping you alive
‪because I believe my daughter is.
‪-Daddy!
‪-Is that you, Min-ji?
‪I took care of the girl's body.
‪Subtitle translation by: Jenny Kim